It's true. Marketing agents are the new
coding agents. Just like coding agents
were such a big deal and people are able
to create software on demand, deploying
marketing agents are so important
because you're able to get customers on
autopilot. [music]
So, how do you actually set them up?
What do they look like? Well, this has
got to be my most requested episode in a
long time. I bring back Cody Schneider
and he shares all the sauce how you can
use codeex or claude code to to build
these. What are the other 20 tools that
you need for the marketing
infrastructure in order to deploy these
marketing agents? And by the end of this
episode, you're going to get your
creative juices flowing around some of
these growth tactics that are going to
help you stand out, that are going to
help you get customers, so that whatever
it is you're building, you don't have to
worry too much about traffic, you don't
have to worry about too much about
revenue, and you can focus on building
an incredible product uh while your
marketing machine is [music] running.
Enjoy the episode.
[music]
Welcome to Greg Eisingberg's podcast
called Sip Baby. I'm your co-host or
guest today. Not co-host. I'm never the
co-host. I'm Cody Schneider. I'm going
to be your guest today. And today I'm
going to teach you how to build an AI
agent that does cold outbound both on
email and on LinkedIn. This is based off
of the comments from last video. If you
want to learn other goto market motions,
you need to comment below right now. Do
it right now. It also helps us for the
algorithm, so you're supporting the show
and it keeps the lights on here.
>> Welcome to the show, Cody. Marketing
agents are the new coding agents. We
only shared one marketing agent last
episode, but the people aren't satisfied
with one. So, you needed to come back
on. You came back quickly. And by the
end of this episode, you're not going to
share one endto-end marketing agent,
right? You're going to share two
marketing agents, how people could set
it up. So by the end of this episode,
people can go stop the video and
actually go set this up and actually get
customers to their vibe coded startup.
Right? This is exactly what I'm
promising you today. You're going to
have two of these in the wild. I'm going
to teach you everything that you need to
know. I'm also going to share all of the
tools that you need. There's no
gatekeeping here. I despise people that
do this. Don't buy a course. Literally
DM me. I'll teach you anything. I'll
just make a public video for everybody.
So let's do it, G.
>> All right. Let's run it. Awesome, man.
All right, so today we're going to build
a system that basically monitors
LinkedIn posts of influencers within
your niche, within your category, and
then it's going to go and extract the
engagers from those posts. Um, and then
we're going to do what's called a
waterfall enrichment to find the emails,
uh, and even potentially the phone
numbers of these people so that you can
then go and do an outbound motion to
them. um doing cold email and then also
uh doing LinkedIn DMs. So that's what
you're is going to happen and then I'm
going to uh teach you how to basically
have it so you can have a agent that's
wired up to both of those inboxes like
managing those inboxes say for example
answering questions or trying to push
them into like booking a demo with you
as an example. So uh yeah man that's
that's really it. Uh the I don't know if
there's any other like specifications on
the high level. I think the only thing
to mention with this is like the
strategy around this. So right now cold
email is getting decimated. Reply rates
are down. Everything is down. Actually
every marketing channel is down right
now. Let's be re let's be real. Uh the
reason is just because like AI slop is
flooding the zone and it's becoming just
red ocean everywhere. Um but the way
that we have found that you can stand
out is you have to look for signals or
triggers that basically show that people
are hand raising um saying hey I want I
want this thing. I have an interest in
this thing. Right? And a great way to do
this is with these LinkedIn uh uh
engagements. Uh they're basically when
they like content that is a a hand raise
or a signal that I am interested in this
you know uh specific thing and from that
we can use that as a way to measure okay
is this my target customer that I'm
trying to sell to and not just like
their firmographics or their
demographics or their psychoraphics
which is like what we would
traditionally use for for outbound. um
this is specifically like no they they
have a propensity or an interest in this
topic and we are going to go and now get
in front of them. Okay. So how do we
actually do this and this is an exact
strategy that we implement for you know
the companies that we're working with.
So I'm going to teach you that right
now. So let me screen share and I'm
going to walk through it. So the first
thing uh that you're going to want to go
to do is literally go to LinkedIn and
find uh influencers within your
category. So, last episode we talked
about AI for WordPress or AI WordPress.
And so, I'm just going to use this again
as an uh the example, you know, like
target demographic that we're going
after. Um, so on LinkedIn, what I would
go do is I would go try and find people
that are talking about WordPress uh
development potentially. Um, let's see
what comes up with that uh development.
And I would try to find posts. This
might actually be a terrible category.
So I we might have to explore something
entirely different, but um I would try
to find posts or creators that are
talking about uh these specific topics
like on a daily cadence, right? Um so
like this like again just for this
example today, this is probably going to
be like a lot of like just not good
signal. So a better way to look at this
is like uh we'll say we'll do AI for or
AI marketing, right?
Um, let's see what comes up and we're
going to try these find these posts
here. So,
>> and what makes a good search? Like why
why was AI for WordPress not good and
why is AI marketing better?
>> Yeah. So, [clears throat] it's really
just like is the content that's being
served what your target customer would
be interacting with? Like that's what
you're trying to get down to here,
right? So like how I would be going
through this and honestly I use the the
for you page of all these algorithms is
so good now that it's like it's going to
show you the content that's relevant
right like this is literally an exact
[laughter]
like perfect like perfect example first
one that comes off it's like awesome
people trying to do some type of video
editing for obvious it's probably for
marketing everybody that's potentially
engaging with this is like a target
customer right so I would say okay cool
I'm going to find these creators and
then I'm going to build a spreadsheet
sheet of all of them, right? Like all of
these people um that I'm going to try uh
that I'm going to source these leads
from. So, right, I would build this
spreadsheet out and we'll just do a
handful of these like from my own feed.
It can even be business accounts and I
think this is the thing that people
don't realize like if there's business
accounts um that the people would be
interacting with that would be your
target customer, that can work as well,
right? So, it can be literally Clay. Um,
and we're going to do the posts from
Clay. And, uh, we'll just keep going
down on this. So, MCP, it's probably too
broad.
>> And you're doing this manually. Like,
you're not using agents to do this. Why?
>> I I wouldn't even typically the company
knows who is interacting. Like when
we're working with a business, right?
They know who their like their target
customer is interacting with, right? So
you can all you need is typically like
10 10 to 20 of these and you have more
than enough to be able to like source
the lead volume that's necessary to
actually make this like a viable
channel. Um you I'm using the feed here
because like what it's going to show you
is what is most like relevant to you. So
it's probably going to be stuff that's
uh you know in your the niche that
you're in. But you can also use the
search for this as well. We used to do
this where we'd like do the search and
we'd find the trending posts from that
period. In reality, it's like there's a
handful of outliers within any niche and
everybody is engaging with those handful
of outliers. If you just monitor those
outliers, you're actually going to get,
you know, 80% surface area coverage for
that entire industry. You don't need
more than that, right? Uh or or it's
it's it it's just like the marginal
return of trying to go for all of it.
It's not it's not there for for that
system. This is the same idea with um we
do this a lot like we try to solve
entropy pro this entropy problem with uh
within like ads, paid ads in particular
where it's like if you just have the
agent like go in this loop, it'll just
kind of make the same ideas over and
over again. How do you solve for that?
Well, you find human creators like 10 of
them on Instagram and you track the
content that they're they're publishing.
You look for the outliers and then from
that you you typically can get signal of
like, oh, here's this new hook format or
here's this new topic and I can just
pull that. I can remix that and that's
the way to do this. So, all right, I
find a handful of these these these
companies. Um, and then from that what
I'll go and do and just for the sake of
uh uh you know the example today, we'll
use Louise as an example. So, we'll say
everybody that interacted with this
post. We're going to use this post as an
example. So um once I have these people
I need to use ampify and I will find the
actual one that we like.
>> And what's ampify for people who don't
know?
>> Yeah. So ampify is a scraping API. So I
can use a single API key and then I can
use it to scrape LinkedIn. Um I can use
it to scrape uh uh Twitter. I can use it
to scrape all of these different
channels. So, it's a way for me to get
data into the context for my agent so
that it can have, you know, awareness uh
and and have that context for it to make
decisions on or make content based off
of, etc. So, okay. So, the one that
you're going to want to use or the one
that we like, we've worked with him like
a decent amount because it's the most
stable connections. There's tons of
these and the challenge with Ampify is
finding good ones that are actually um
uh like being monitored and being
maintained. And so this uh uh this guy
API maestro has a ton of these for
LinkedIn. You can see all of these here.
It's all of these different functions
that you can do. So how appy functions
is you get an API from ampify and then
this enables for you to be able to have
your coding agent like cloud code or
codeex call from uh ai or call the app
through the appy to one of these
endpoints that are here. So, uh, for
example, you can do this post scraper.
Uh, for the one that we're going to do,
it's going to be engagements. So, let me
find that. Uh,
post reactions on LinkedIn. I believe
this is it. This is exactly it. Yep. So,
post comments and then post reactions
are the two that you're going to use.
And what this enables you to do is
everybody that has engaged with that
post. So, the post that we are just
looking at here. So, everybody that's
interacted with this and commented on
this, we're going to be able to pull
this out. And I'm going to show you how
you can actually do this in uh Cloud
Code right now. So, I'm just going to
spin up a terminal real quick. And let
me reshare my screen. And so, I have
that uh I have that Appify API key um in
uh already saved locally within the
directory that I work out of for uh all
of my growth work. And if you don't know
what I'm talking about here, I have a
whole video on my uh channel that's
basically a crash course into how to do
this. It's called go to market
engineering or marketing engineering. It
will walk through the entire setup
process. Takes about 10 minutes. But
basically, this ampify API key is shared
here. And I've already written this
script. I had the agent go and read how
do I use this endpoint to pull out all
of the post and comments information,
the all the people that have interacted
with this. So I can give it this post
URL and I can say extract the engagers
using the ampify API key
and it's going to go and run that
process for me. So this is how I would
go and build this automation or build
this agent as I would basically take
this code and I would deploy it into the
cloud and I would say okay on a daily
cadence I want you to check for net new
posts. So that is where I would look at
the profile posts. So this is the
profile post scraper. So I would extract
the post urls from this person,
right? So every net new post daily is
getting extracted and then from that I'm
then extracting the engagers
using that API endpoint as well. Right?
So right now as you can see the duped by
public profiles there's 63 raw and it's
about to pull all of those contacts out.
So once I have those contacts this is
this is done man like game over.
As long as you have the LinkedIn
profiles, you can go and find the email
addresses of them. You can find the
phone numbers of them. You can find
everything that you need on the cold
outbound. And I'm going to show you that
right now. What are the tools to
actually go and use to do this? Um, so
let me just show you though again just a
uh the final completion of this. And
what makes this an agent versus a
marketing automation?
>> Yeah. So the agent component of this is
that it is running on a cron job daily
and then you're going to have an agent
that's later on we'll have it responding
to the inbox and this is this blurry
line right like what is an agent people
ask me this every sales call and the
answer to all of this is like it's how I
think about it personally is it's
something that's doing a job to be done
right so the job to be done here is
finding leads and outbounding to those
leads and then responding to those leads
as they're like asking questions or
again like driving them deeper into the
pipeline. Um in reality though g like
what is a market like what is a
marketing agent? It's it's code. It's
maybe some thinking loop and it's a live
data stream, right? That that is really
how like this functions. And the thing
that you can make, you know, extend this
further with is like what you're who
you're outbounding to. Um you want it to
basically do an ICP fits or is or or a
target customer segment fit. So before
it even does this enrichment that we're
about to do, you would be like, "Okay,
agent, research this person and the
company that they're at. How many
employees do they have? All of these
things." And then based off of what we
find, if it fits this customer profile,
like it's you're going to have the agent
basically think through that, right?
Using an LLM, if it fits this customer
profile, then it goes into this
enrichment. Then we're actually going to
cold email them. So that's where that
thinking loop could potentially be here
as well. But really the the blurriness
between all this I think about it as
software anymore like to be transparent
like everybody the thing a different way
to say this is like everybody tried to
put God in a box and give it access to a
Facebook ads account and we realized
that is not the right way to do this
whatsoever. The right way to do this is
like what was the human doing? They were
running this very specific process with
like media buying. They were researching
ad creative angles. They were making new
ad creative. They were testing the new
ad creative and then they were like
pruning the losers, promoting the
winners, right? Like that is what the a
top media buyer does. Okay, how do we go
and make a piece of software that does
that exact same thing? So when you hear
agents like really just think software
with potentially a thinking loop like
you shouldn't be paying a different like
way to think about this and this is
something I'm obsessed with right now.
You should not be paying anthropic. You
should not be paying Chad GPT to do an
API call. You should be paying them to
make the software that uses CPU to do
the API call. Why are you paying this
tax on tokens every time that you're
trying to do this marketing activity?
That's ridiculous. Build the software
that does the solution for you, not
tokens burning every time that you're
trying to do the action. So anyway, um,
okay. So we've got these LinkedIn URLs
and what do we do with them now? So
we're going to do what's called a
waterfall enrichment. And so we're
basically going to use these LinkedIn
profiles to go and find the email
addresses and then the phone numbers of
these individuals. So how do we do this?
The first thing that we're going to use
in a tool stack is called getleads.io.
Um so this is a database of uh it's
basically they aggregate all these B2B
contacts and you can access it via their
API.
um the emails that we don't find within
git leads, we're then going to use
something or we're then going to
waterfall down to something like Apollo.
Um and then you could take this even
further down into something like
Origami. It's another tool that we have
been using and experimenting with. Also,
their team is just doing awesome work.
Like Finn and his whole team is
incredible. So anyways, for git leads,
let's go back to our uh u uh our
terminal right now. So again, this is me
hands on keyboard doing the process to
teach it to you. But everything that I'm
doing right now, this is all just going
to be code under the hood. And once it's
code, I can deploy that into a cloud
system. As long as it has the necessary
data that it needs and the necessary
access that it needs, it can go and run
this operation autonomously. And then
you're just there basically jockeying
the agent or modifying the system.
Right? So we're building a system here.
So from here um what I would then go do
is say use the get leads API
uh to uh find the emails and phone
numbers
>> and like dumb question.
>> Yeah,
>> that's legit like f you know like
it's not gray to get these people's
emails. It's like fully legit.
>> It is fully legit to get these emails.
um what you do with those that's where
things uh like from a compliance
standpoint change. You can cold email
technically in the United States. You
can also add people to a email
newsletter um to be and be can spam
compliant. There's like tons of you like
things you basically have a checklist of
things that you have to do. With this
said though, um like this is one of
these like on the cold email side and
the contact lookup. Um you're basically
just buying data from a data broker
which is is legal, right? That that is
accessible. So these companies how they
do this is they basically are buying all
these lists and then aggregating them
from all these different data brokers.
That whole piece is it's a whole other
shady network. But this uh like what
we're talking about here, you know, on
the spectrum of like black hat to white
hat is pretty far on that white hat
side. So
>> cool.
>> Yeah. I mean, I don't think anyone
would, you know, mistake you for a
lawyer also.
>> Oh, totally. Take this with a grain of
salt, you know, and and like there's
also different compliance rules within
the United States.
>> Your own research.
>> Exactly. Exactly. Within, you know, the
United States versus uh like the EU has
totally different compliance pieces.
>> Exactly. Um but with that said like the
uh you know the finding of people's
information and then like reaching out
to them uh there you c you can do this
basically is kind of the high level but
again this I I we don't have time today
to go into all the the specifics about
like all this the finite details here.
So once I found this um each of these
individuals and then the emails um from
there what I'm then going to do is
validate these emails. So I would send
it to a software called millionverifier.
So million verifier um enables me to uh
basically check if the email is good,
risky or bad. Um you know more technical
terms would be uh like good, catchall,
um you know risky etc. Um the the
reasoning for this or the reason you
have you want to do this is the emails
that come out of these providers. So out
of git leads, out of Apollo,
out of Origami. I think they do some
checks like a little bit deeper though.
So you I don't know much as much about
this, but I know for sure with get leads
in Apollo, it's like do the second
verification. You're basically only
wanting to send cold email to valid
emails because if you send to invalid
emails, you're going to basically just
run into deliverability problems. And
probably right now you're asking
yourself like, "Okay, cool. Well, how do
you send these cold emails? I'm going to
show you that in a second, so bear with
me. So, we've done that waterfall
enrichment. We found the emails. We
found the phone numbers. And when I say
a waterfall enrichment, what is
happening here is we're taking that list
of 50. And just to use this spreadsheet
as an example, so say we have, you know,
50 that we have uh 50 LinkedIn URLs that
we found and on git leads, maybe we only
find, you know, 32 emails
of those people, right?
So that next cohort, so those other 18
that are left, I'm then going to send
those 18 to Apollo. So of those 18 that
I send, maybe I only find 10.
And then those eight, that's when I
would send that to something else like
Prospio or Origami or these other
enrichment tools. And the reasoning
behind this is you're you're starting
with what is the cheapest, most accurate
and then moving your way down into the
more expensive uh uh validation tools.
Um but from this you can pull out
basically from a list like you know this
is the way that you get to uh you know
an 80% fine rate etc. And you can chain
as many of these together as you want.
Um it just you know depends on your
budgets that are available etc. There's
also aggregators of this like Origami as
an example like aggregates this
waterfall for you. So you can just send
them a LinkedIn profile and it's going
to like waterfall through the options
that are available. Um, okay. So the
other other thing to throw in here that
will be valuable to your team is a
software called Lead Magic. So this is
one that I we use a lot for like mobile
phones in particular. Um, but same
strategy here. Uh, it's just basically,
you know, another enrichment tool. Uh,
but specifically on the phone number
side, we we've used it a decent amount.
So once I have that contact information,
I now need to go and actually build this
outbound motion. So on the cold email
side first, how do we go and do this? Uh
we need to buy inboxes. So a couple
different ways to do that. I can use a
tool called inbox kit. I can use
instantly AI's pre-built uh uh like
emails that you can buy from them. Um or
I can use uh a company called Hypertide,
which is the partner that we use and we
work with. they are some of the best
info in my opinion. So when you're
buying these emails, uh you're buying or
you're really what you're doing is
you're buying inboxes and domains that
are burner domains that enable you to
send cold email
um not from your core domain. And the
reason that you have to do this is so
that you don't burn the deliverability
of your core domain. So what do I mean
by that? If you send from you know your
exact domain um and uh you know say we
send 10,000 cold emails from that um we
will nuke the deliverability of the
business URL the actual domain that we
use to you know run our company right
you don't want to do that so typically
what you want to do on the marketing
side is have this se have this
separation so you have domains that are
for your cold email you have domains
that are for your email marketing you
have domains that are for your
transactional marketing so This would be
or transactional email. So this would be
email that's being sent directly from
the product to a customer. Imagine like
a password reset as an example. And then
you want to have your business you know
domain email which is what your team
actually uses to run the company etc. Um
so with Hypertide as an example um we we
have a partnership with them. So it's a
little bit different but uh we can send
about 10,000 cold emails. Uh just to
give a a um you know kind of the cost
breakdown here. We can send about 10,000
cold emails with them for about $100 a
month in infrastructure costs on the
inbox side. Um it's about the same for
majority of these. So inbox kit as an
example is very similar pricing. They
also run like sales all the time. So
look for those on the domain side. So
you basically buy the domains and then
you're paying a subscription to have
these inboxes hosted for you. And then
on instantly side u you can typically
get started with this $97 a month tier.
in total, you know, out the door to get
going on this, the infrastructure cost
can be in that range of about $100 to
get started or sorry, about $200 to get
started for the sending uh software and
then also the inboxes. So again, just to
reiterate this because I know I've
talked through a lot, I'm pulling the
lead list from LinkedIn. I'm finding
these people. How do I know that these
are people that I want to reach out to?
It's because they're engaging with
content that I know my target customer
would be interested in. And so these
people are basically hand raising that
they are would potentially be my target
customer,
>> which is insane by the way.
>> Right. Which is insane to
>> find this, right? [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> It's impossible to find this. Um and so
the uh so I'm finding these people. I'm
then doing a waterfall enrichment to
find all of their uh contact
information.
And then once I have their contact
information, I need to actually be able
to send to them. So I'm getting inbox
infrastructure to be able to send. And
then I'm sending with a platform like
instantly. And then on the LinkedIn DM
side, what I'm sending with is a
platform um like hey reach.
Another one that we like is called Bot
Dog.
Um both of these have APIs. Um, but what
these enable you to do is basically uh
do uh LinkedIn DM campaigns um from
these accounts. I also know people that
are just like using LinkedIn DM or sorry
LinkedIn inmail for this and seeing
incredible success right now uh using
this strategy. So again just throwing
out all the strategies that are
available. Um so this is how you can
build this pipeline right now. How do
you actually like have an agent that is
managing that inbox? So looking at
instantly as an example, they have an
API
and that API
allows for you to monitor and manage the
entire account. So you can have an agent
that's literally writing copy for each
individual email or person that you're
contacting or reaching out to um and
writing those variables and then that
can be basically pushed into instantly.
So this happens outside the platform
gets pushed in. But the bigger thing
here is they also have web hooks. So
when a positive reply happens, you can
send that web hook confirmation back to
your agent that's hosted on some type of
cloud server and that agent you give it
basically um like a base prompt, right,
of like you're the goal like here's all
the context that you need and your goal
is to try to get people to schedule
demos on you know this this link, right?
It can manage that inbox, answer
questions, push people deeper. But the
thing that gets really fascinating and
really powerful with this G is like it
can do these follow-ups like months
later, right? So it's like okay like
also like every six months, right? I
want to pro it grow program that in to
like re reereach out to these people
that went cold. I can also plug it into
my scheduling application like Kalanley
or like Cal.com.
I can give the agent access to see okay
did this person that we reached out to
can we did they actually schedule a
discovery call did they actually you
know produce the action that we're or
you know make the action that we're
trying to optimize for and so from this
you can basically build this like SDR in
a box right that is again finding new
people for you based off of the
engagements that they're interacting
with on social finding the emails
actually writing the emails, deciding if
this is a good ICP fit, and then sending
that to these sending platforms and then
managing the inboxes of those sending
platforms. And again, when I say agent,
right, like when I'm saying, oh, it's
managing this inbox, it's literally just
code under the hood, right? It's code
under the hood with an LLM attached.
That is an agent. Like in this context
here, you don't have to over complicate
this. You don't have to have God in a
box managing an email inbox. Be a very
simple setup to actually produce this. I
also get asked this question a lot like
do you need use like some agent
framework under the hood it's like a lot
of the times you don't need it it's just
bloat you can just have a very simple
like a very simple solution for these
finite problems right it doesn't have to
be this over complicated or
overengineered thing so anyways happy to
answer any questions about that or dive
deeper on any of this again it's hard to
show code so I I didn't really do that
today of like this is how you do it but
what you need here basically the final
piece is you need to set up a server so
use something like a railway or this is
what we do at like graft right? Is like
we have the data pipeline warehouse and
then the server to deploy these agents
to that's like off of the live data
streams. But yeah, happy to answer
questions. D
>> I mean to be clear, you're you know
you're using a harness like Cloud Code
or Codeex to actually build out all of
the thing. But this the hard part is the
strategy around you know who you're
going after, why you're going after
them, what's your tool stack that like
what's amazing is you just like outlined
here's all the tools that you need to
get like set up then it becomes okay I
have to go into you know that's what
people are talking about software
factories like we're all in the software
factory business now right because we're
just going and we're spitting up stuff
like this the software to actually go
and complete these tasks.
>> Absolutely. I I think the thing that we
are like focusing on like so to say like
a good way to think about this is like
if you can build it in cloud code and
like have some type of local system that
you're running, you can probably deploy
that to a server somewhere, right? And
have that run on an hourly cadence or a
daily cadence or whatever that ends up
looking like. The challenge ends up
being how do I set up the infrastructure
that's necessary for the agent to be
able to do this right and the the the
solution is like the open source
solution as an example like we talked
about this on the last call use
something like a uh with click house to
get like create your data pipeline and
your data warehouse so you have that
data stream for the agent to make those
decisions and then you have to have some
server and like when I say server what
do what is that right for the
uninitiated it's just a computer that is
on [laughter]
all the time somewhere else that you're
putting code onto, right? I think this
software factory thing is super
fascinating as well. Like like really
it's funny. This is how I'm thinking
about marketing now. Like marketing is
just code like a like when I generate
[laughter] a banana image. Like that's
just a JSON prompt under the hood. Like
when I make like you know seed dance AI
avatar videos that's just like an LLM
that like scraped Reddit like read some
things wrote a script and then we it's
just an API call that's happening to Kai
AI to generate that image with like okay
here's how you chain this together to
make it into 30 seconds every everything
now like in and my co-founder this is
his firm belief like Max always says
this he's basically like the only agent
is a coding agent actually [laughter]
everything else is this software that's
being made by the coding age and I think
this is like this paradigm shift and
like something that we are obsessed with
like why are you paying tokens for
things that can be just code that is
running on super cheap compute you don't
you don't have to have like inference
every time that you're doing this action
only use inference when you need it and
this is kind of this like differing
viewpoint that I think you know
everybody's just like oh token abundance
I'm going to token max I'm like I'm
actually totally like probably the
opposite of that like why it just feel
it is wasteful like do the thing that is
the simpler thing that has less
likelihood of breaking. Like if you have
Hermes try to run your Facebook ads,
high likelihood it might just like
absolutely nuke the account, but if you
have it run based off you you build a
piece of custom software for yourself
that's running based off of a system
that a normal human like a real human
would run totally different, you know,
outcomes that you're going to get from
that that are probably higher quality.
So,
>> okay. Do we have time for a second
marketing agent demo flow? Yeah, I can
talk through um I just did this for
[laughter]
um I just did this for my team. Um I I
don't know if that'll be super
interesting actually. I mean you tell me
we basically we're like okay how do we
at scale make social content on LinkedIn
for like the entire team and like so we
have them like basically we're
interviewing them we take the
transcripts we pull out the insights the
insights get written into the posts the
posts automatically get scheduled to
their LinkedIn accounts using a tool
called ordinal uh MCP
>> yes stop like yes this is interesting
because a lot of people I mean a lot of
people might have heard you know listen
to this cold cold email approach
approach or cold reachout approach and
are like m I want to go the organic
route. So like what's what's an example
of setting up a marketing agent in an
organic route and and can you break that
down for us?
>> Absolutely. Yeah, I'll do the LinkedIn
one because it's super topical and like
we've had a lot of interest in this
lately by companies which has been
pretty fascinating. They're using this
with like their sales teams like they
want, you know, their seven person sales
team to be posting daily. How do they
actually do that and make unique ideas?
So um this also pairs with the cold
email. I'll talk about that as well. Um,
but yeah, just to run through the
process. Uh, super simple. Um, it's like
literally record a conversation like
this. Like I have a a a weekly call like
one-on-one with like the people that
we're doing this for in the or just like
tell me everything that like you've
learned in the last week. I just
basically interview them, have a
conversation, right? It doesn't have to
be anything like you don't have to have
any focus. It's just like what are the
things that that jumped out at you after
being in these sales calls or whatever
your job is. You can do this for like
technical people as well at the
organization. You can do this for
everybody. And I imagine this is how the
large like the real companies are doing
this. There's no way that like everybody
at like a lovable [laughter] is writing
the content that's going out across all
of the accounts. Maybe that's happening.
But um I think what's more likely is
that there's somebody behind the scenes
that's orchestrating this. It also
doesn't have to be an interview. It can
just be sales calls or internal comms.
Like Alex Lieberman as an example has
been talking about about this a lot
where they're they're basically sourcing
like so much context is happening within
their notion within their codebase
within their their Slack. We see this as
well, right? You can use one of these
agents to query those data sources,
right? Like query the sales channel um
or query the gong transcripts and that's
where you can pull these insights from.
And honestly, a lot of the times you
find that it's really inside like it's
really good content that's trapped in
there. Like these ideas like for
example, a customer had uh you know, a
customer said that or a potential
customer said this and it was like why
they didn't buy the product and that can
turn into an unbelievable piece of
content um that you can extract from. So
you get source material. Why do you have
to get source material? The reason is
because if you go and you try to just
have the agent like think about this,
you're like, "Write good LinkedIn
content." [laughter] It's going to be
the most mid thing you I mean, it's
you're going to waste the person's time
on the other side, right? Um or you're
going to get flagged for AI slot by
LinkedIn's new feature that just
released this morning. Um the the better
way to do this is source this from real
human conversation because that's where
these original ideas are coming from.
Um, another example of this is like
literally this podcast. You could
extract all the insights from the
transcript and that can be used as
social content. This is like a strategy
I use for myself. But it doesn't have to
be just your own. It can be somebody
else's as well. It can be, you know, a
podcast with Naval. It can be whatever.
It can the source material can be
anything. But the system that you create
is some type of source material that's
happening on, you know, some type of
cadence. And then from that, I'm I'm
building basically this writing and
scheduling process. So, what I I'll walk
through now how to actually like do
this. Um, so take that source material.
You're going to do an API call um into
uh you know some LLM as an example uh
for this. Like you could I mean we've
even used just like uh Claude Sonnet as
an example and it's probably good enough
on the writing side. Um and then once
you have that those written posts,
you're then going to go and use
scheduling tool. We like Ordinal for
this. um they're a partner of ours as
well. Um but it allows for you to have
multiple LinkedIn accounts connected to
it and then they can also interact with
each other which is amazing. Um but you
can through their API or their MCP
schedule these posts to each of the
individual accounts
and then Ordinal also has and I could
just go into this actually show you um
Ordinal also has uh the uh analytics
data that pulls in from your LinkedIn
post there as well. So we can see the
breakdown of like which content is
actually performing well. So it has the
analytics of the multiple accounts. You
can actually see the breakdown of the
individual posts and that data stream
can go back to the agent so that it
understands okay this is what's getting
impressions. This is what's doing well.
Let's go do more content like when it
does its cycles of writing that can
influence the next round of creative. So
topics like this perform better based
off of the source material we pulled.
How can we snowball or remix? use those
specific words snowball or remix to have
it go further, right? And this is where
the LLM is thinking on top of that data
stream. And when you look at like what
is happening here, like what does the
social media manager do? I actually
think the social media manager job like
full stop. It's it's [laughter]
I think it's already dead, but let's
won't get into that. If you're listening
to this, please learn how to make and
manage content at scale across multiple
accounts. um it's with agents cuz that's
going to be I think that's the real meta
now is like how can a single person
manage you know 10 20 100 accounts
across all of these different channels.
Um but when you look at what a social
media manager did previously like a good
one that was actually excellent
excellent at their job is they would
prospect for ideas. They would make
content about those ideas. They would
publish it. They would look at the data
to see which got the most impressions
and then they would turn that into a a
recurring content calendar where they're
like, "Okay, I'm just remixing this
these same ideas over and over again."
If you look at my Twitter like post as
an example or even my LinkedIn, it is
the exact same thing remixed every 90
days like full stop. That is all that's
happening. And that when you get enough
information like a big enough corpus,
you have you basically understand what's
already going to go viral. Like I I have
these posts that I've literally used for
the last two years. Every time I post
it, I know it's going to go viral. I
can't post it every day. You post it
every 90 days, right? And that's how you
can go back into this cadence. And so
again, have this mentality of I'm
prospecting for ideas. I'm prospecting
for winners. Once I find those, I'm
trying to use those as as often as I can
because I know that that's what's going
to work. That is what the audience is
resonating with. And this is this
applies to product as well, right? Like
when I think that a lot of first-time
founders, they they spend time thinking
about like I'm trying to get the market
to buy this and in reality it's like I'm
try the the the pros at this is like
what does the market want to buy? Can I
build it and can I sell it to them?
Right? Like that is actually how you
start a business. And it it for some
reason it's this this flipped thing
where they're like, "Oh, I'm trying to
invent a new idea." I don't want to
invent a new idea at all. Well, I want
to be like, what do people want to buy
that currently like they can't buy and
can I go and figure out this the way to
build that thing? And then I know I can
sell that back to them. I know it's the
market is going to be receptive to and
you need to think about content in the
same way where like what is the content
that the market is currently receptive
to and by mining that content from other
sources that has already had a viral
moment. This is a way to leaprog that to
identify that and then you're going and
you're putting your own spin. You're
putting your own, you know, angle on
this. So anyway,
>> lot of thoughts there. Um, agreed on the
social media manager is like that role
is dead or it's evolve. It's going to
evolve like it's going to evolve into
the social media agent man manager. So
you're going to need to be able to spin
up agents so that you can create a bunch
of accounts on the fly that
systematically creates content like you
have. Like you get millions of
impressions a month, free impressions.
actually the platforms are paying you
which is insane to do it. It's insane.
And
>> I get paid to build lead pipeline. Like
think about that.
>> It's crazy.
>> And like I I it's so funny, man. I'll
talk to like founders or like you know
large like people that that run bigger
companies and they'll they'll be like
why are you why would you would you
invest in social? And I'm like look at
the earned media. Like if you were
paying for those impressions on
platform, for example, on LinkedIn, it's
like $22 per thousand impressions is the
average, right? So like every post that
you get, even with an account that's
like 500 followers, you can get a,000
impressions. That's like $20 that you
just like put into your pocket for free,
right?
>> But but it's it's so there's the earned
media side and then there's also like
the platforms pay you. Like YouTube
literally pays you to do marketing for
late checkout. Like what the what the
hell? [laughter]
>> It's crazy. It's crazy. And then, you
know, for the people who are like,
"Well, I don't want to do a personal
brand." Makes sense. What Cody is
suggesting is like have people on your
team have these personal brands. And if
you don't, and by the way, I'll give you
a piece of sauce. If you don't want to
do that, another really uh smart thing
to do with agents creating content for
you is creating theme-based pages or
topic based pages. So, for example, my
good friend uh Julian Shapiro, you know,
he had a company, a growth agency called
Demand Curve.
>> Absolute goat, by the way. His blog is
incredible and that's what I came up on.
So, I'm just like one of
>> I actually grew up with Julian.
>> No, did you really? That's amazing.
>> Yeah, he was like my name.
>> He was like a farm now or something,
right?
>> Yeah. That's awesome.
>> Yeah. So, I need to get him on the pod.
that uh Julian being the smart guy he
is, it's not like he created a uh X
account that was slash demand curve. I
mean maybe he has that, but he actually
created an ex account called at Growth
Tactics.
So he's creating content on this growth
tactic page. People interested in growth
tactics follow it and then they learn
about his agency and his products,
right? That's social media company. And
like again, it doesn't it could be I
mean there's the ones that are my
favorite are like Chase passive income.
I don't know if you've seen this.
>> Yeah.
>> Um they're doing it more as a meme page,
but like you can use like this attention
that you can garner for free as a way to
drive inbound for whatever whatever it
is that you're building. It doesn't have
to just be you. It can be this like
anonymous thing that is still providing
value that you're aggregating and you
know organizing for the internet, right?
So I'll leave it there. I don't know.
>> Really,
>> uh, you know, impactful marketing agents
that you just broke down. Um, I wish we
had 40 hours together and we did like a
crazy comment below. That's the only way
I come back. That's the only way he'll
have me. All right. So, you have to do
this. You have to comment what you want
to learn. I'll take I'll teach you
whatever you want. It can be how to
build social media agents like for Tik
Tok clouds. It can be like, "How do I
actually run a paid ads account?" It can
be anything that you can imagine. It can
be direct mail. I'll literally walk you
through how can you send direct mail at
scale by scraping Google Maps. You name
it. How do you advertise on TV and
what's the meta there? Uh like how do
you get cheaper clicks on LinkedIn? I I
can break down any of that. So, I
appreciate you, Cody. We'll see you in
the comment section. Like always, I'll
include links for where to follow Cody
on the internet in the show notes in the
description. Can I shout it out? She
give me give me the opportunity.
>> Go for it.
>> Hell yeah. Go find me on Twitter,
LinkedIn. That's where I'm the most
active. And if you want to deploy these
exact agents that I talked about today,
go to graph.com. Uh we have both the
platform solution for this and also we
forward deploy software engineers to do
these actual implementations on our
platform. We would love to help you. If
you're a fast growing company, that is
who we're seeing the most success with.
So thanks for having me, G.
>> God bless you, Cody. I'll see you next
time.